A very good afternoon train more bag with
another only question Dashrath question of the
day in the too much questions are left to have
15th August welcome you two years question
so subscribe mission impossible 4 wheeler
new question a question half a minute and
authority will take loan from 10 m and
entertainment from last switch on side and
come join our
more who can do what now and by giving your
answer you can learn exciting prizes
and you can
also ask your family and friends who are part of your life to
participate in this you can
become a part of this campaign by joining us
you can take a small step to make your day just
and can always join now along with this
you also have a chance to win a
give pen for yourself and your family members
and the most interesting thing is that we
give you a question every 2 hours every day now participate in it  You
can, in the same way, we have
5 questions throughout the day, you can participate in all five of these
questions
and join us,
you can see this question on your screen,
I will give it again, then you Mr.
Right in the snow authority and people that
role, you will be difficult to learn
from 10 am, take in the chair reviews and
get ready to make the dawn moh antique tone
from in this section, last switch on is the
evening lies and question duration, what will you do
in this situation and you can understand,
send on daily basis
that today there are sales, you can see that and at
10:00 pm our show comes, Branch Speaking,
you come and join it and see your results
and what is the interesting thing is that
you have a chance to win more than one multiple gift, by
joining this,
this is not just a quiz contest,
this is a step in that direction, we have to learn about
our roles, as
you have  See, I told you that the
name of our show itself is Drive for Mission
Possible. We have to make this machine possible. We have to
make our roads just. So now
we can also have coincidences in this. We
can take a step forward in making our roads just. This has been accomplished so
that we
can connect as many people as possible with us and express them on
their roles because roads are
for everyone. Somewhere or the other you are
connected to them and it is very important
that all of us, whether it is
people walking or those working or those
riding two-wheelers, should be safe for all of them.
Somewhere or the other it becomes everyone's
responsibility if they are on the road to
make it safe. So we would
request you to help us
in taking this entire campaign forward and
in making our roads just. If
you have ever seen in other countries, in other countries,
you see how
well people follow the rules
because  They understand another thing that
all these rules and regulations that have been made are
not for anyone else,
if they follow those things then it will be
best for their benefit only. We would
request you that if not for others then
stay safe for yourself and your loved ones and
follow all the rules. It is very important that
you follow all those rules so that
we can make our lives more
safe and we can reduce the number of road accidents that happen on a daily basis. So to
join this campaign
and to be a part of this campaign,
you come and answer the questions.
You can go down below in this screen below you
and register your answer.
You can register only once for one answer and
now you can get a chance to win an exciting gift.
Safety rules which are invisible
to the people outside have understood. In such a situation, when we will
understand that we should not do this to show off to others but for
our own safety and the safety of our loved ones
because of your value, the
validation of your life.  It is more important for your
family, for your
parents than for you, so
we want you to take care of yourself for their happiness
and follow all the rules
and if you are
going for a short distance, please
wear a helmet and Sohail madam, always
buy an ISI marked helmet and
wear it tight, it should have a certificate, it should
not be loose, if it is
not tight then it will
not fit, if you feel something then it will be
loose and if it is tight then it will be
uncomfortable for you which can
destroy you, while driving, so
it is requested that you always
buy an ISI marked helmet, it should be absolutely tight
and always wear it after putting the belt on,
if you are going by car then it is very appropriate of you,
it is not necessary
that you will wear it only if you are driving,
if you are a companion or
sitting on the side then also it is
very important for you to wear a seat belt because it can protect you from any
kind of accidents
and  Your life can be saved
Yo Yo this thing aka Ajju we all
know that not only we ourselves but
our children also
need to follow all these rules so
we should teach them how because
in the coming time they will also be an important part of
this road they will also drive so
we have to make them aware of all these things so that they can
stay safe on the road as I said about
tube wells and it is
very mandatory for them to wear helmets similarly
if you are going in roads then it is very important for those
who are with
strangers also have a responsibility
it is not that if they do or
they do not like or try something then there is no
response for them Britain of course
responsibility you are a part of that thing if
you are going home on the road then it is your
responsibility too that you should always
cross the road on zebra crossing
you should always cross the road from the top and always use the foot over bridge
or the passes that are made
for crossing the road, do not run and cross the road
suddenly like this  Don't cross the road because it can be
harmful for both you and others because the cars
and two-wheelers and vehicles which are coming on the
routes are a hundred percent behind you
and if you suddenly
shrink on the road and start running from here then it is
a problem, they
cannot brake immediately and their breed is still
high, so the risk of accident becomes very
high, it is possible that the
brakes may not be applied immediately, another bike coming from behind or hitting the
front due to my bike or even if one
hits the bike then the speed of the people behind them may
not reduce, so I request you that
whenever you cross the road, you should always check first
that there is no
change, only then do it, I
request you that you should always cross the road using the speed limit
and use the foot overbridge, if
you are passing through Andhra, use the
foot crossing route, so
if we all perform our responsibilities
well then we
can succeed in making our roads safe, this is a question of
morality, this is a question  The
question is for you, you should participate in it and involve
your family and friends in
it as well and win exciting prizes. The
authority will start
from the phone,
take additional reverse and key to make the turn, move ahead
and taken from the intersection and
switch on the warning light and make a
join in this with us and just do your research.
Now you
can also answer the questions by visiting our website.
You will find it at the bottom of your screen, you
can go there and answer and win exciting prizes.
Download it and involve your loved ones in it as well
and become a part of this campaign
and take this entire work forward. Make
your bread and butter safe, make your loved ones safe,
make your family safe. It is that when
you use the road every day, your
process, your awareness,
your concentration is very important.
When you are driving, you should
know from the first things in your mind that what you have to do, if you  If you choose
this as an option everyday, you will also get
confused and the people who
drive around you can also get confused, so
keep your mind clear, do
not do any distraction while driving on the phone because your
carelessness can cause harm to someone else as well.
They request you that if you are
driving then drive at
low speed and if you
drive normally then keep in mind that
according to the people, you should concentrate on your settings and
your thoughts and do
not let them get distracted and they
request you that when any such person is
driving or is sitting beside you or
any Madan Gara child is
sitting, then what happens to him is that the
distraction levels increase which
sometimes become your distraction
and if you are talking on the phone,
talk on Bluetooth only, of course
when you talk on the phone then somewhere or the other there is a
distraction in the mind,
they request you not to do such things, keep
yourself safe, focus completely and
Drive with concentration and
keep yourself and your family safe every day and be careful that your carelessness can cause harm to others.
Being a responsible citizen, it is
your responsibility to take
care of yourself as well as others. Suraj five and the question
you must write don't know authority and
noel road you will depart from the check and
boss and kid was to make a sentence from which
lies and the question of the amazing
Rafi this in this Suraj thing that question after two to two
answer this question on
meeting price and give china ne ka wicket you
that you will remain on join us
till a pilgrimage of temporary this camp in is this will run
suite you were listening to 1 goodbye to avasana
active under teacher question thank
you so much stay tuned stay healthy status
and follow the rules thank you so much for j&k